https://www.furytriad.com/privacy-policy/

About Pooks
Pooks and Her Dys-Brain and the Character Who Stole It From Her
Pooks & Fandom
FAQ [Warning: Facebook Involved]
Prithee & Gramercy Press
For Writers
Privacy Policy
Navigation
Home »
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
I must confess that my pigeons outsource their deliveries, whether they be newsletters or blog entries.
The following privacy notice states what has always been and continues to be policy on this site until further notice; no changes are anticipated in the foreseeable future.*
Privacy Notice
Effective Date:  May 5, 2018
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for Patricia Burroughs and my website; https://www.furytriad.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website, except where stated otherwise. It will notify you of the following:
What information I collect;
With whom it is shared;
How it is secured;
How policy changes will be communicated; and
How to address concerns.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
Short version:
I collect little and share none.
Long version:
I am the sole owner of the information collected on this site.
If you contact me via a form on my website, I will only have your email address.
If you subscribe to my blog, I will only have access to your email address by going into the automated process that sends you blog entries, but it is not something I ordinarily see, nor would I collect your email address to use for a different purpose.
If you sign up for my newsletters I will only have your email address.
Orders
I am in the process of creating a webstore on this site. No info will be collected here. You will follow links to Amazon, to Gumroad, or elsewhere. I will never see any of your information unless specifically noted. [Example: If you purchase an autographed book I would of course have to have an address to mail it to you. To think otherwise would be silly. But again, that information will not be shared or used for any other purpose.]
To be clear: I do not sell, share, give,
bend, spindle, or mutilate your email address
or any other of your information in any fashion
because I am not that kind of girl.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may easily opt out of any future contacts from me at any time. On every newsletter you receive from me you will find a way to unsubscribe at the bottom. On every blog entry you receive via email you will find a way to unsubscribe at the bottom.
Security
Any information you submit to me on this website is encrypted and transmitted in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page.
Cookies
WordPress software uses “cookies” on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to improve your experience here.  f you don’t want cookies stored for my site or others, your browser preferences should allow you to make that choice. I certainly don’t mind!
Some of my business partners may use cookies (e.g., Amazon and Gumroad). However, I have no access to or control over these cookies.
I’m told that aboutcookies is a good guide to deleting and controlling cookies if you want to know more.
Links
This web site [furytriad.com] contains links to other sites. Please be aware that I am not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. I encourage you to be aware when you leave my site and to read the privacy statements of any other sites that collect personally identifiable information.
Surveys & Contests
From time-to-time my site may request information via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.
*Notification of Changes
If I have reason to update this Privacy Policy it will be posted on this page. Thus, I advise you to review this page periodically for any changes. Changes will be effective immediately, after they are posted on this page.
If you have any questions or suggestions about my Privacy Policy,
do not hesitate to contact me via email at pooks at furytriad dot com.
A-D-H-D! Oh! Look! A Mystery! Available now, and readers are raving! This Crumbling Pageant is Only $4.99 Everywhere! My Book ProgressUntune the Sky, Volume Three of The Fury Triad32.2%Revenge of the Killer FlamingosPhase:Writing100%Remember, Remember...Phase:Week 1Due:4 weeks26.4% Random Quote
“I’ve had a perfectly wonderful evening, but this wasn’t it.”
— Groucho Marx
Let My Pigeons Fly This Blog to You
Join 1,731 other subscribers
Email Address
Subscribe
Tickle the Pigeon to Receive the Newsletter My New Magical Addiction!My new addiction--a monthly subscription to Owlcrate and all the fabulous YA Fantasy swag [including an autographed book every month] I can squee over! Click the picture to see for yourself! [This was the February box, all for $29.95 sans postage.] Follow me on TwitterMy Tweets From Goodreads What readers are saying about The Dead Shall Live
Reviews from Goodreads.com
Always have an audiobook with you!
Follow me on TwitterMy Tweets Pigeons love Siteground.
Looking for Something?
Search for:
Tags"We Shall Overcome"
May I Send You My Newsletter?
My pigeons deliver the latest Fury Triad news, sales and contests on an 'occasional' basis.
SUBSCRIBE!
You have Successfully Subscribed!
